so
good afternoon everyone i am adrika
and now it's finally time for our next
question
question number four of the day which in
total which
will be our 49th question so now without
any further due let's just
uh start by discussing our question
so you are driving on broad
daylight on a blind spot you will
a stop check carefully and proceed
b reduce speed and honk
to indicate that you are coming or c
continue to drive as it is safe during
day time
or d increase your speed to pass quickly
so what is happening here basically is
that you are driving and you know
all around there is like full daylight
you know the sun's rays are falling
everywhere and there is a full clear
view because
there is a lot of light but uh you know
there is a lot of light but you are
driving
on a cars blind spot you are driving on
a blind spot of another vehicle
so in this situation when you are
driving
and there is a lot of daylight a broad
daylight
uh and but you are driving on
uh on some on another vehicle's blind
spot
what will you do a stop
check carefully and proceed you will
first
stop your vehicle you will you will
carefully check
that everything is fine or not and then
you will proceed
and uh just continue your driving
or b reduce speed and
home to indicate that you are coming uh
you will reduce your speed and then you
will
honk to tell the other vehicles driver
that
you are there you are coming or
see continue to drive as it is safe
during the
time or you will not do anything and you
will just continue your
driving as usual because uh you think
that it is safe or to drive
during daytime because there is a broad
daylight so
it is safe to drive or d increase your
speed to pass quickly
you will just simply increase your speed
and then you will just pass
uh pass by that vehicle quickly
so i'll just once again uh repeat this
question
so you are driving
uh you
[Music]
so you know uh
with this small step of answering this
question we can do a lot
so i will just like to uh you know
i request you all to answer this
question you know
the answer uh as this question is valid
only for two hours
uh you know it's valid for two hours and
we can actually make a difference we can
get awareness save lives of people on
roads and make our roads safer with this
simple step
of answering these questions you know uh
because
by this simple step
[Music]
you know situation
so in case you know
actually make a situation
how your behavior should be there on the
roads
in certain situations so you know this
can actually make a difference you can
learn a lot
[Music]
like if we talk about only this question
uh youtube question blind spots
he bought up blind spots blind spots are
the places
where a driver cannot completely see you
know
uh a driver
whenever it is required the driver
should look
behind their shoulders left and right
and left and right
because those places are called the
blind spot
uh or as a situation
right
[Music]
so i will just once again repeat this
question
so you are driving on
broad daylight on a blind spot
you will a stop check carefully
and proceed be reduce speed
and home to indicate that you are coming
see continue to drive as it is safe
during daytime
or you know
[Music]
foreign
see continue to drive as it is safe
during
day time driving as usual normally
continue
[Music]
it is safe
so you know hope
i hope that all of you had answered our
previous questions as well
and you will be answering this question
also you know it does not take a lot of
your time
and uh seeks of them
you know it doesn't take a lot of your
time also
or the easy be answer karna or you say
you know it's chorizo
is
then you know we start changing
ourselves
and try and take another step
uh in making our roads
safer
[Music]
is
so you know you can win some exciting
prizes either a bike safety kit
or a car safety kit so you know if this
are a benefit sam
and that is why i would like to just
tell you all
about achilles
[Music]
you know every day these types of
questions will be coming
every day we are taking five questions
every day
uh and they will be coming on a gap of
two hours so after every two hours
a night a new question will be coming
and each question is also valid for two
hours
like abhi or abe
question hey so uh you know the next
question will come in the
next two hours so
like this every day we are taking five
questions
and that is why i would like to just you
know request you all keep in mind
at least
[Music]
or
as well uh and that is why i will just
request all of you to answer in
all the questions which will be coming
also is
[Music]
fifth question i got other
so now i will just once again repeat
this question
so you are driving on broad daylight
on a blind spot you will a
stop check carefully and proceed
b reduce speed and honk to
indicate that you are coming or c
continue to drive
as it is safe during play time or
d increase your speed to pass quickly
so if say uh bots are your benefits
[Music]
in making sure that our indian roads
become
safer thank you everyone